http://www.concretesociety.co.za/about/legal-notice

Website Legal Notice
Members Log In
MenuAboutAbout UsContact UsOffice BearersNewsCOVID-19LinksLegal NoticeMembershipCategories and FeesApplication FormsIndividual MembershipAcademic MembershipCompany MembershipCompany MembersPlatinum Company MembersGold Company MembersSilver Company MembersBronze Company MembersMembers SectionMembers LoginMembers Section MenuStudent Members SectionBranchesBranch Programme of EventsInland BranchEastern Cape BranchKwaZulu Natal BranchWestern Cape BranchReport Back of EventsInland BranchEastern CapeWestern CapeKwaZulu-NatalNationalBranch CommitteesBranch CPD RegistersPublicationsConcrete BetonTechnical Journal OnlineOpen Access PapersSource BookPublications For SaleSource Book
Fulton AwardsHistory and OverviewRecord of Fulton Award Winners2019 Fulton Awards - WinnersEventsCONCRETEFiX The SeriesConferences
CPD RecordsEvent HistoryPresentations and CPD recordsFAQ'sCementConcrete - FreshConcrete - HardenedStudents' RegisterStudents LoginACI
About
Website Legal Notice
CONCRETE SOCIETY OF SOUTHERN AFRICA NPC   (Concrete Society)
1. WEBSITE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USAGE
1.1 Please read the following Website Legal Notice carefully as it contains the terms and conditions of usage (“Terms and Conditions”) of the Concrete Society website located at www.concretesociety.co.za (“Website”) owned by the Concrete Society of Southern Africa NPC ("Concrete Society") as well as other important legal notices applicable to the end user accessing the Website (“User”) or (“You”)
Enquiries: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Your usage of the online information services contained on the Website constitutes Your acceptance of the Terms and Conditions contained below and Your arising obligations towards the Concrete Society. The Concrete Society may amend these Terms and Conditions at any time by posting the amended terms and conditions on the Website. The amended Terms and Conditions shall automatically become effective immediately after they are posted on the Website and any subsequent use of the site shall be governed by such amended terms. These Terms and Conditions were last revised on 31 March 2011. You are advised to check these Terms and Conditions regularly for any amendments or updates.
Enquiries: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Limited Liability of the Concrete Society: The User understands that usage of the Website is at the sole discretion and risk of the User. The Concrete Society reserves the right to change or discontinue any aspect or feature of the Website, including, but not limited to, content, hours of availability, and equipment needed for access or use. Despite taking every effort to maintain the availability and accessibility of the Website, the Concrete Society takes no responsibility for and will not be liable for the Website being temporarily unavailable or inaccessible.
1.2 No Warranty: The information contained on the Website is provided by the Concrete Society and/or its partners, suppliers or agents without warranty of any kind, expressed or implied, including (but not limited to) any implied warranties of reliability, fitness for any particular purpose, timeliness, sequence, completeness, non-infringement of third party rights and/or freedom from errors or inaccuracies as far as permissible by law.
1.3 Indemnification of the Concrete Society: You agree to defend, indemnify and hold the Concrete Society, its officers, directors, employees, agents, licensors and suppliers, harmless from and against any claims, damages, actions and liabilities including without limitation, your loss of profits, direct, indirect, incidental, special, consequential or punitive damages arising out of the use of or inability to use the Website or the software supporting/enabling the Website and any legal and accounting fees, resulting from or alleged to result from Your use of this Website or the software supporting/enabling the Website.
1.4 Unauthorised use of the Website: The User is permitted to use the Website for lawful purposes only. Unauthorised use of the Website includes posting or transmission of data which violates or infringes in any way upon the rights of the Concrete Society or third parties, which is unlawful, defamatory or otherwise objectionable or which constitutes advertising of goods or services in the absence of written approval from the Concrete Society. Unauthorised use of this Website may give rise to the Concrete Society instituting a claim for damages against You and/or You may be found guilty of a statutory and/or criminal offence and/or be liable for civil damages.
1.5 Website Links: The Website may include links to other websites. These links are provided for Your convenience for the purposes of providing further information. Such links do not indicate that the Concrete Society endorses the website(s) linked to. You agree that the Concrete Society is not responsible for and does not bear any liability in relation to the content of the linked website(s).You may not create a link to this Website from another website or document without the Concrete Society’s prior written consent, in which case the terms of linking to the Website shall be governed by the terms of Your “Linking Agreement” with the Concrete Society.
1.6 Applicable Law and Jurisdiction: You consent to the jurisdiction of the Magistrates Court of South Africa for the adjudication of any legal dispute between the Concrete Society and You. This Website Legal Notice will be construed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Republic of South Africa.
1.7 Severability: If any provision of this Website Legal Notice is found to be invalid by any court having competent jurisdiction, the invalidity of such provision shall not affect the validity of the remaining provisions of the Website Legal Notice, which shall remain in full force and effect.
1.8 Website Intellectual Property: This Website comprises of software and content (such as text, articles, images and photographs, video, trademarks, (all names, marks, brands, logos, designs, trade dress, slogans used on/in connection with the website) and trade secrets that is the intellectual property of the Concrete Society and/or various third parties subject to the intellectual property/other laws of South Africa and as applicable foreign laws, international conventions and treaties. Further, and to the extent that the Concrete Society does not own specific content or such content falls within the public domain, the Concrete Society may hold copyright/further intellectual property rights in the selection, co-ordination, arrangement and enhancement of such content on the Website. No license to the Concrete Society’s intellectual property or the intellectual property of third parties has been granted to You unless otherwise indicated. Without limitation to the prohibitions placed on the User by contract or law and subject to 1.9 You expressly agree not to:
1.8.1 Reproduce or use the aforementioned intellectual property either in print or electronic form in violation of the intellectual property rights of the Concrete Society and/or such third parties as applicable;1.8.2 commercially exploit, reproduce, distribute, transmit, display, publish or broadcast any Website intellectual property without prior written approval of the Concrete Society or in the case of third party content, the rights holder of such intellectual property;1.8.3 not to claim or convey ownership of Website intellectual property either in its entirety or otherwise;1.8.4 modify the Website content for the purposes of reposting to other websites;1.8.5 alter or remove any trademark, copyright or other notice from the Website content; and1.8.6 copy, store, or otherwise incorporate Website content or intellectual property into any other web site, electronic retrieval system, publication or other work.
1.9 Unsolicited Commercial Communications (spam):  You agree not to collect or use any Personal Information of Users of the Website and/or members of Concrete Society for the purposes of transmitting and/or facilitating in the transmission of unsolicited commercial communications.
2. CONCRETE SOCIETY INFORMATION AND WEBSITE COMPLIANCE
The following table contains further information on the Concrete Society and represents the information that must be provided by the Concrete Society to You in compliance with Section 43 of the Electronic Communications and Transactions Act. This section of the Website Legal Notice was last revised on 31 March 2011. You are advised to regularly check this section of the Website Legal Notice for any amendments or updates.
Enquiries: This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
The full name of the Concrete Society:
Concrete Society of Southern Africa NPC a non-profit, Public Benefit Organisation established in accordance with the Companies Act of South Africa.
Concrete Society’s physical address and telephone number:
275 20th Avenue, Villieria, Pretoria, 0186
Tel: 012 348 5305 / 1319
Concrete Society’s website and e-mail  address contact addresses:
http://www.concretesociety.co.za
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Membership of any self-regulatory or accreditation bodies to which Concrete Society belongs or subscribes:
American Concrete Institute (International Partner)
Engineering Council of South Africa (Voluntary Association)
Cement and Concrete Institute (Associate Member)
The registration number of the Concrete Society
Registration Number: 1996/009468/08
VAT Number: 4250268945
The place of registration:
South Africa
The names of Directors
Prof. W P Boshoff  – National President (2020/2021)
The physical address where the Concrete Society will receive legal service of documents:
275 20th Avenue, Villieria, Pretoria, 0186 Tel: 012 348 5305 / 1319
Description of the main characteristics of the products or services offered by the Concrete Society:
The Concrete Society offers its members technical seminars and conferences, networking opportunities, site visits, publications, members’ services directory (the Source Book), social interaction, voting rights. All focused on concrete.
The full price of goods or services, including transport costs, taxes and any other fees or costs:
Please see the webpage notices posted from time to time for the relevant costs.
The manner of payment:
Payment may be effected via bank deposit, internet transfer or by cheque.
The terms of Agreement, including any guarantees, that will apply to the transaction and how those terms may be accessed, stored and reproduced electronically:
As set out in this Legal Notice.
The time within which the goods will be dispatched or delivered or within which the services will be rendered:
The Concrete Society shall confirm the customer’s order within 30 days after the day on which the Concrete Society received the order, unless the parties have agreed otherwise. Where the Concrete Society has failed to execute the order within the agreed period, the customer may cancel the agreement with seven days' written notice
Where the Concrete Society is unable to perform in terms of the agreement on the grounds that the goods or services ordered are unavailable, the Concrete Society shall immediately notify the customer of this fact and refund any payments within 30 days after the date of such notification.
The manner and period within which consumers can access and maintain a full record of the transaction:
Contact This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it. to enquire about records.
Alternative Dispute Resolution Code:
You agree that in the event of a dispute or alleged breach of the terms hereof You will work together with the Concrete Society in good faith to resolve the matter internally by escalating it to higher levels of management prior to resorting to arbitration where both parties agree to resort to arbitration.
The security procedures and privacy policy of the Concrete Society in respect of payment, payment information and personal information:
See Privacy Policy.
The minimum duration of the agreement in the case of agreements for the supply of products or services to be performed on or on-going basis or recurrently:
The duration of subscriptions and advertising agreements are as set out under the webpage Rates and Data.
Specific services or reports are offered once-off.
The rights of the consumers in terms of Section 44 of the Consumer Protection Act:
You have the right as our customer to assume that in the case of any goods that we sell to You, we have the legal right to sell You those goods.
3. PRIVACY POLICY
The following table contains important information on the Concrete Society’s Privacy Policy and includes the various consents and permissions provided by You to the Concrete Society in respect of use of Your Personal Information. This section of the Website Legal Notice was last revised on 31 March 2011. You are advised to regularly check this section of the Website Legal Notice for any amendments or updates.
3.1 Privacy and Personal Information:
3.1.1 The Concrete Society endeavours to comply with all laws and regulations governing privacy. As such, The Concrete Society seeks to ensure the quality and accuracy of personal information in its possession and compliance with South African law.3.1.2 The Concrete Society shall not be obliged to ascertain or provide the identity of the sender of any messages or content.
3.2 Personal Information Collected, Principle of Minimalism and Purpose of Collection: Please be assured that the privacy of the Concrete Society’s Users is of the utmost importance to the Concrete Society. The Concrete Society collects, processes and stores personal information of its Users subject to the following principles:
3.2.1 Relevant and minimal personal information of Users is collected for the purpose of managing User’s communications with the Concrete Society. Users warrant that all personal information supplied by them with regard to an electronic transaction is both true and correct. In the event of any aspect of your personal information changing, it is your responsibility to immediately notify the Concrete Society of the changes. Notification must occur via an email sent to This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
3.3 Handling of Your Personal Information:
3.3.1 To prevent unauthorised access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the appropriate use of information, the Concrete Society has in place policies and procedures to protect the personal information the Concrete Society collects about the User.3.3.2 Users acknowledge that records relating to the provision of Services and personal information may be required to be retained in terms of law, operational purposes and for evidential reasons by the Concrete Society. Users expressly agree to such processing, retention and necessary access to such records.3.3.3 Further, the Concrete Society may use the contact information to provide the User with information in relation to events, services and/or products offered by the Concrete Society.
3.4 Disclosure of personal information: the Concrete Society may disclose personal information
3.4.1 to comply with the law or with legal process;3.4.2 protect and defend the Concrete Society’s rights, equipment, facilities, and other property;3.4.3 protect the Concrete Society against misuse or unauthorised use of the Website; and/ or3.4.4 protect other Website Users or third parties affected negatively by the relevant User’s use of the Website.
Contact Us
+27 12 348 5305 / 1319
+27 82 514 2560 / +27 82 779 0368
This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Privacy Statement
Copyright © 2020 Concrete Society of SA
Members Login
Please login to activate the Members Section menu bar
Remember Me
Log in
Forgot your password?
Forgot your username?
Cookies
We may sometimes use cookies, which is a small text file that a website saves on your computer or mobile device when you visit the site. It enables the website to remember your actions and preferences over a period of time, so you don't have to keep re-entering them whenever you come back to the site or browse from one page to another. Enabling these cookies is not strictly necessary for the website to work but it will provide you with a better browsing experience. You can delete or block these cookies, but if you do that some features of this site may not work as intended.
If you wish to restrict or block web browser cookies which are set on your computer or mobile device, then you can do this through your web browser settings. The Help function within your browser should tell you how. CSSA collects, stores and uses this information in order to compile non-personal statistical information about browsing habits, click-patterns and access to CSSA's online services.
UA-8457802-24
AboutAbout UsContact UsOffice BearersNewsCOVID-19LinksLegal NoticeMembershipCategories and FeesApplication FormsIndividual MembershipAcademic MembershipCompany MembershipCompany MembersPlatinum Company MembersGold Company MembersSilver Company MembersBronze Company MembersMembers SectionMembers LoginMembers Section MenuStudent Members SectionBranchesBranch Programme of EventsInland BranchEastern Cape BranchKwaZulu Natal BranchWestern Cape BranchReport Back of EventsInland BranchEastern CapeWestern CapeKwaZulu-NatalNationalBranch CommitteesBranch CPD RegistersPublicationsConcrete BetonTechnical Journal OnlineOpen Access PapersSource BookPublications For SaleSource BookBrowse Online Source BookFulton AwardsHistory and OverviewRecord of Fulton Award Winners2019 Fulton Awards - WinnersEventsCONCRETEFiX The SeriesConferencesYCRETS 2021Future Concrete 2020CPD RecordsEvent History
Presentations and CPD recordsFAQ'sCementConcrete - FreshConcrete - HardenedStudents' RegisterStudents LoginACI
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience on our website.
Accept
More information
